So your goal for this quiz, is to finish
你在这个练习的目标 是完成
modifying the crawl_web procedure, so that instead of returning just
修改 crawl_web 过程 使之不仅返回
the index, it returns both an index and a graph.
索引 而是同时返回索引和一个关系图 (graph)
And the graph gives the link structure. The graph should
该图 (graph) 给出链接的结构 应该
be a dictionary, where the entries in the graph are
是字典格式 该图 (graph) 的条目是
a URL, which is the target page, and a list.
一个 URL 也就是目标页面 以及一个列表
Which is the pages that link to that target. So
即链接到目标页面的页面列表 那么
to test your graph making code, we've provided a sample
为了测试你的 graph 制作的代码 我们提供了一个示例
site at this URL. So if that's the link
网站 在这个网址上 所以 如果这是你
that you pass in as the seed for the crawl_web.
作为种子页面传入 crawl_web 的链接
It's going to crawl in the site we set up.
该过程将在我们设置的站点抓取
And there's an index page that looks like this, it's
有一个这样的索引页 在其中
got five links on it. And, those links go to different web pages. So the first
可以获取 5 个链接 然后 这些链接到不同的网页 那么第一个
one goes to my favorite hummus recipe. So, there's a link from
链接去到我最喜欢的鹰嘴豆泥食谱页面 所以 有一个从
index.html. And it goes to the page hummus.html. And if we
index.html 开始的链接 它转到页面 hummus.html 如果我们
follow that link, we get to a page that
点击这个链接 我们得到一个网页
has no links on it. This second link. Goes
上面没有链接 这第二个链接 去到
to page arsenic.html. And that page includes a link
arsenic.html 页面 该网页包含一个链接
the Nickel Chef page. And the Nickel Chef page
去到 Nickel 厨师页面 然后 Nickel 厨师页面
includes a link to kathleen.html. And that page has
包括 kathleen.html 的链接 该页没有
no links on it. And the third link on
其他链接 然后是第三个索引页的
the index page, also goes to the kathleen.html page.
链接 也转到页面 kathleen.html
And there's two more links on the start page.
开始页面上还有两个链接
The first one goes to the Nickel Chef page,
第一个进入 Nickel 厨师页面
which we've already seen. And the last link, goes
我们已经看过了 然后最后一个链接
to the Zinc Chef. And from the Zinc Chef
去到 Zinc 厨师页面 然后在 Zinc 厨师
page, we have two more links, we have one to
页面 我们又有两个链接 其中一个链接到
the Nickel page. And we have one to the Arsenic
Nickel 页面 还有另一个是到 Arsenic
Chef's famous hummus recipe page. So this is a pretty
厨师的著名鹰嘴豆泥食谱页面 所以 这是一个相当
complicated link structure, although it's very simple compared to the
复杂的链接结构 尽管它已经比我们在网络上
things that we actually find on the web. But your goal
实际找到的要简单得多 但是你的目标
is to be able to produce this graph, by modifying
是能够产生这种图形 通过修改
the code that we have for crawl_web. And then once
我们已有的 crawl_web 代码 然后一旦
we have the page ranks, we'll be able to use
我们将网页排列好 我们就能够使用
PageRank to find the best page. To find a hummus recipe.
PageRank 找到最好的页面 找到鹰嘴豆泥配方
So for this site, the graph that your
对于这个网站 你的 crawl_web
crawl_web should produce, should have entries that show these
产生的 graph 应该有条目显示这些
connections, so there should be an entry where the
关系 所以应该有一个条目 其中
URL is the urank/index.html, I'm leaving out the beginning
URL 是 …urank/index.html 我省略了
of the URL. And the entries should be a list of all the pages that, that links
网址的开头 然后这些条目应该是 该网址上的所有链接的列表
to there. So they're going to be five pages. All
因此 它们是 5 个页面 所有
five of these should be in the list here.
这五个链接应该在这个列表中列出
There should be the Hummus page, there should
应该有 Hummus 页面 应该
be the Arsenic page, and the other three pages.
有 Arsenic 页面 以及其他 3 个页面
The order that. Links appear in this list doesn't
链接出现在这个列表中的顺序并不重要
matter, it's correct as long as you have all
只要你将 index.html 页面能够链接到的
five of the links that you can reach from
5 个页面全部包含在内
the index.html page. The kathleen.html page, doesn't have any
就是正确的 kathleen.html 页面没有任何
outgoing links, so the entry for kathleen.html should be
外部链接 所以 kathleen.html 条目应该是
an empty list. So see if you can figure
一个空列表 所以 看看你是否可以找出
out how to change the code for crawl_web, to produce as its second
如何更改代码 crawl_web 以产生它的第二个
output, a graph that shows the structure of the web pages that we crawled.
输出 —— 显示我们抓取网页结构的关系图 (graph)